https://www.bennett.edu/administration/business-finance/information-technology/terms-of-use/

Contact
F.A.Q.
Give to Bennett College
National Alumnae Assoc.
Give
Privacy Statement/Terms of Use
Home Administration Division of Business and Finance Information Technology Privacy Statement/Terms of Use
Published December 2016
The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the Bennett College website (http://www.bennett.edu).
Information Gathering
On occasion, the College uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website by identifying which parts of our site are most heavily used, and what percentage of our audience comes from within the Bennett network. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that user sessions will be tracked, but the users remain anonymous.
Our staff monitors search terms that users enter into the Bennett College site search engine, but this tracking is anonymous and never associated with individual users. The tracking data is used to generate statistical reports on usage and help us tailor the Bennett College website to user needs. Site usage by individual IP addresses is never disclosed and logs are retained on a temporary basis and then deleted from our systems.
There are numerous forms on the website for entering personal data to provide an appropriate focus for expressions of interest in and inquiries for admission, financial aid, etc. This information is transferred via email to the appropriate department. Bennett College does not share, sell, or give this information to anyone not affiliated with the College. The information is used for the express purpose of ensuring that users receive satisfactory responses to their inquiries and requests.
Security
The Bennett College website contains links to other independently run websites within the Bennett network and to some sites outside the “bennett.edu” domain. In general the College is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In the case of the link to contribute.com, which allows donors to make gifts in an online environment, the third-party contractor that administers the transfer of funds manages the personal information required for each transaction in a secure setting and with due regard for individual privacy rights.
The College and website have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. If you have any questions about this privacy statement or about the practices of this site, please contact:
Laurie D. Willis
Chief Communications and Marketing Officer
Bennett College
900 E. Washington St.
National Council for the Accreditations of Teacher Education
Southern Association of Colleges and Schools – Commission on Colleges
F.A.Q.
First Year Student Advising Process (Course Selection)
First Year Student “How To…?”
Scope of Service
What is Academic Advising?
Freshwoman to Internship Support Program (FISP)
Ready To Join the Sisterhood?Join thousands of women who have changed the world!Get Started Now
